<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<speakers>
    <speaker>
	    <fullname>Chen Shixin</fullname>
		<nickname>Sting Chen</nickname>
		<company>2Style4You</company>
		<position>CTO</position>
		<desc>TopGeek Fuounder, Now employed at 2Style4You.com - a global leading modern technology company. Master degree in Computer Department from Shanghai Jiao Tong University in 1999. 13 years of experience of Internet technology and products，founded PMCamp community, also active in ThinkinLAMP，ShanghaiOnRails，CPyUG，GTUG and etc.</desc>
		<avatar>chenshixin.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Keynote - Python Enriches the World</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Shen Wei</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company></company>
		<position></position>
		<desc>A senioir python developer, author of eurasia - a high efficency server. Founder of 湖州迅普信息技术有限公司; co-founder and CTO of 广州遛宝计算机技术有限公司.</desc>
		<avatar>shenwai.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Python, the Road to The Future</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Lin Wei</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>Netease</company>
		<position>Senioir technology manager</position>
		<desc>Netease senioir tech. manager，17 years of experience of programming.</desc>
		<avatar>linwei.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Python Exploration and Discovery of Game Development < /speech>
	</speaker>
	
    <speaker>
	    <fullname>Hung Qiangning</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>Douban</company>
		<position>Chief Architect</position>
		<desc> Chief Architect of Douban, first full time employer of Douban.  Working on embedded systems, after graduating from Tsinghua University.  Start to use python from 2002, becoming a software engineer from hardware engineer. Has solid understanding  of how a computer programming language works at lower system level. </desc>
		<avatar>hongqiangning.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Python Application and Innovation at Douban</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Damien Hou</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>Google</company>
		<position></position>
		<desc>Google has the highest level of python developers. Founder of Python – Guido is at Google. Damien is from Slide, a Google Company.</desc>
		<avatar>damienhou.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Scale web application stack with coro-thread</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Pan Junyong</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>润普科技</company>
		<position>Founder, CTO</position>
		<desc>One of pioneers in python community, held Zope Chinese community in2002 , founder of润普公司. Starting Internet software in 2007, released 易度云办公 everydo.com, specialized in enterprise cloud office application.</desc>
		<avatar>panjunyong.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Technical inside of Everydo PaaS Cloud Development Platform </speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Huang Dong</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>Tudou</company>
		<position> Technology  VP </position>
		<desc> Dong Huang  is currently employed as Technology VP at Tudou. In Charge of design and running many large scale high volume product and system. Is also co-founder and active with FreeBSD、Python communities, One of the founders of 啄木鸟Community, is also actively helping many start-up projects.  He created彩虹流量 and xBaynet product series.</desc>
		<avatar>huangdong.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Metering and Bandwidth Management in Large Scale Website</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Chen Zheng</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>Sina</company>
		<position></position>
		<desc>Engineer at Sina.com development center, in charge of R&D of system platform, Multiple years of research and work experience of paradigm of cloud computing. From 2009, focused at new generation of could computing, Sina SAE(SinaApp Engine)  and could storage service, focused at scalability and reliability of programs, automated testing and designing of computer language.</desc>
		<avatar>chenzheng.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>《SAE(Sina AppEngine) 的 python 版实现》</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Ryan Ye</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>Google</company>
		<position>Tech Lead and Senior Software Engineer</position>
		<desc>
		<![CDATA[Specializing in developing web applications, social network games and iPhone apps. Interested in server architecture and game engines. 
		<br /><strong>Specialties:</strong>
		<br />- Web application architecture design and performance optimization
        <br />- iPhone application development
        <br />- Game and graphic programming
        <br />- Engineering management
        <br />- Major programming language: Python, Javascript, Objc, ActionScript
        <br />- Familiar with Perl, C/C++, Java
        ]]>
        </desc>
		<avatar>ryanye.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>《A Python approach to implement Schemaless model on MySQL》</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>CCP Games</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>CCP Games</company>
		<position></position>
		<desc>CCPGames is the second largest company in desktop games , also very strong in Internet games. There are many Python talents in the company </desc>
		<avatar></avatar>
		<speech>Python Development at CCP Games </speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Li Yinghui</fullname>
		<nickname>Limodou</nickname>
		<company></company>
		<position></position>
		<desc>Founder of Python Chinese community and one of the key activists in Python, Author of popular editor - Ulipad , author of web framework – Uliweb.</desc>
		<avatar>liyinghui.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Thoughts and Practise in Web Framework Development - Uliweb </speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Lai Yonghao</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>江苏盛典</company>
		<position>CTO</position>
		<desc>Senior developer in Internet Games, Rich experience with python game development. Icon producnts: New generation MMOCAT《天下盛境》 and etc. Founder and one of the organizing group of Tech Slalom Pearl Delta.</desc>
		<avatar>laiyonghao.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Python Usage in Web Games </speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Wang Jian</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>广州黑崖网络科技有限公司</company>
		<position>GM and CTO</position>
		<desc>广州黑崖网络科技有限公司总经理兼技术总监。</desc>
		<avatar>wangjian.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Python Usage in Medium Role Play Game Servers</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Zhou Qi</fullname>
		<nickname>Zoom.Quiet</nickname>
		<company>KingSoft</company>
		<position>Process Improvement Manager </position>
		<desc>Founder/Admin of Python Chinese Community , devoted in acitivies non-for-profit python community ,  AKA. Big Mummy, OBP and designer and host of 蟒营工程;participated and host many online/offline activities; producer of  “Lovely Python”; 坚持用 Pythonic 感化国人进入 FLOSS世界进行学习 / 分享 / 创造！Now employed at KingSoft</desc>
		<avatar>zhouqi.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Light Talk: 解耦应用开发 Based on MQ</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Wang Jianfeng</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>OpenERP</company>
		<position></position>
		<desc> Starting opensource ERP(Enterprise Resource Planning) in 2005, touched many opensource ERP product. Held and joined  Chinese translation for weberp, openbravo and openerp. Started to localize and introduce OpenERP (Original known as TinyERP).注重基于开源+威客的商业服务模式即实现程序员参与开源的长短期收益。现集中精力做OpenERP的远程二次开发团队，Python is cool at ERP二次开发，Enjoy it……  The owner of http://openerp-china.org/ and project manager  of http://code.google.com/p/cloudteam/ 
Webibo: http://weibo.com/opennewbazaar ,  Interests: ERP, opensource and威客</desc>
		<avatar>wangjianfeng.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Light Talk:  Intro to OpenERP Solution and Extenstion</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Diao Lizhi</fullname>
		<nickname>Adieu</nickname>
		<company></company>
		<position></position>
		<desc>Independent programmer, Python Lover, Interested in Django and web development,  Solving problems with small python programs in leisure .</desc>
		<avatar>diaolizhi.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Light Talk: Improvement of Xunlei Offline with Python - A Python Successful Story</speech>
	</speaker>
	
	<speaker>
	    <fullname>Li Jundong</fullname>
		<nickname></nickname>
		<company>阿里云</company>
		<position></position>
		<desc>11 years of experience,  8 years of side jobs with Python. Starting from DOS age, growing with Windows desktops, catching the fashion of the web, moving forward to cloud age. </desc>
		<avatar>lijundong.jpg</avatar>
		<speech>Light talk:  on the Journey with Python</speech>
	</speaker>
</speakers>
